# John Oluwatobi Abidoye

+234-8068746276 | Abidoyejay@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/oluwatobi-abidoye-4826b9224

## WHAT'S DIFFERENT ABOUT ME

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs.

Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, team-work, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

## **RECENT WORK HISTORY**

# Lead Developer - DopAdvert Technologies Ltd.

Jan. 2022- Present

- Organizing team Members to create high quality user-centered Responsive Website
- Created and Develop Frontend Website
- Trained other Junor developers
- Implemented prototyping & consistent design pattern across web & mobile version

# Frontend Development(Intern) - SideHustle Internship

April. 2022 - May 2022

- Learning Frontend basics and i was able to complete a Project using HTML, CSS
- Working with the Team Members to implement the group Project
- I was awarded a Scholar Badge and Certificate for my Performance

# **Graphics Designer - Darek's Foundation**

April. 2021 - Present

Designing of Designs for the Foundation using CorelDraw, PosterMaker and Figma

Frontend Developer(Intern) - Lustre Agency Ltd.

Dec. 2021- present

- Learning Frontend and working with other Frontend developer to improve my Learning
- Working with the design Team to implement Project like Flyers.

Product design(Intern) - Zuri inc.

May. - Jul. 2022

- Completed full UI design & prototyping of Logistics app in 2 weeks with tools that aid fast-paced work during 3 month of training in Zuri
- Solved a user problem by user research and case study

# Portfolio - Sardiusportfolio.netlify.app

# **SKILLS**

**Design:** HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | Git | Github | Netlify | Vercel | Figma, Canva, PosterMaker, Pixlab, Sketch & CorelDraw |

**Non-Design:** Technical Writing | Business growth | Research | Content writing | Volunteering | Teaching | Microsoft Office

**Projects:** Fast-paced, Waterfall & Agile development | Communication | Collaboration | Teachability

**Motivation:** Kindness | Excellence | Innovation | Functionality | Empathy | Helpfulness | Usability

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering -Federal University - Oye-Ekiti

## 2017-09 -Current

Machine Learning – Coursera

Active and recognised member of the Google Developers Club

Machine Learning – Coursera	2020 - Current
Google UX design – Coursera	2022-Current
SQL Fundamentals – DataCamp	2022-Current
User Experience(UX)Fundamentals - Udemey	2022
Fundamentals of HTML & CSS - Udemey	2021
CERTIFICATIONS	
Jobberman Soft-Skill Certificate	2021
Great Learning - Frontend Development (HTML)	2022
Great Learning - Product Design (UI/UX)	2022

2020 - Current

Udemey - Fundamentals of HTML & CSS 2022

Coursera - Car Transport App in Figma 2022

LINKS

**Twitter** - <u>www.twitter.com/SardiusJay</u>

**GitHub** - <u>www.twitter.com/SardiusJay</u>